import 'package:quiz_app_tutorial/models/question.dart';

List<Question> java_questions = [
  Question(
    question: 'Q. What is the extension of compiled java classes?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      ' .txt',
      ' .js',
      ' .class',
      ' .java',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. Which exception is thrown when java is out of memory?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      ' MemoryError',
      ' OutOfMemoryError',
      ' MemoryOutOfBoundsException',
      ' MemoryFullException',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. Which of these are selection statements in Java?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      ' break',
      ' continue',
      ' for()',
      ' if()',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        'Q. Which of the following is a superclass of every class in Java?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      ' ArrayList',
      ' Abstract class',
      ' Object class',
      ' String',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. Which of the below is not a Java Profiler?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      ' JProfiler',
      ' Eclipse Profiler',
      ' JVM',
      ' JConsole',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        'Q. Which of these packages contains the exception Stack Overflow in Java?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      ' java.io',
      ' java.system',
      ' java.lang',
      ' java.util',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        'Q. Which of these keywords are used for the block to be examined for exceptions?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      ' check',
      ' throw',
      ' catch',
      ' try',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. Which one of the following is not a Java feature?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      ' Object-oriented',
      ' Use of pointers',
      ' Portable',
      ' Dynamic and Extensible',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. Which environment variable is used to set the java path?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      ' MAVEN_Path',
      ' JavaPATH',
      ' JAVA',
      ' JAVA_HOME',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. What is not the use of “this” keyword in Java?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      ' Referring to the instance variable when a local variable has the same name',
      ' Passing itself to the method of the same class',
      ' Passing itself to another method',
      ' Calling another constructor in constructor chaining',
    ],
  ),
];
